My name is Sebastian.
我叫塞巴斯蒂安。
I welcome you to our
我欢迎你到我们这里
self driving chronology.
自驾车年表。
The self driving car
自驾车
started when I was 18.
我18岁时就开始了。
One of my best friends in the
我最好的朋友之一
neighborhood died in a traffic accident.
邻居在交通事故中丧生。
His life went away in no time.
他的生命很快就消失了。
And back in the day, I asked myself,
回到白天，我问自己，
why is it that we have these machines
为什么我们有这些机器
that are great on one hand,
这一方面很棒，
but still kill so many people?
但还是杀死了这么多人？
It stuck with me for a long time.
它困扰了我很长一段时间。
And when I joined Stanford in 2003,
当我2003年加入斯坦福大学时，
the US government
美国政府
had just launched a competition
刚刚发起了一场比赛
called the DARPA Grand Challenge.
被称为DARPA大挑战赛。
It's a competition where a self driven
这是一场自我驱动的比赛
car had to drive through an empty desert
汽车不得不穿过空旷的沙漠
in California.
在加利福尼亚。
Our car Stanley,
我们的汽车斯坦利，
named after Stanford was a blue,
斯坦福以蓝色命名，
beautiful Volkswagen Touareg.
美丽的大众途锐。
And lo and
而且和
behold we won the competition.
看哪，我们赢了比赛。
My team joined Google in 2009 to build
我的团队于2009年加入Google进行构建
a self driving car that could drive
一辆可以驾驶的自动驾驶汽车
on public streets where we all drive.
在我们都开车的公共街道上。
And when we were ready to
当我们准备好的时候
tell the public about it,
告诉公众，
we had driven not just 100,000 unique
我们驾驶的不仅仅是100,000个独特的
miles for the self driving cars.
自驾车的里程。
But we've also driven pretty much
但我们也开得很多
the hardest streets in California you
加利福尼亚州最难的街道
can imagine, completely self driven.
可以想象，完全是自我驱动的。
We drove from San Francisco
我们从旧金山开车
to Los Angeles.
到洛杉矶。
The technology has been in
该技术已经存在
development for many, many decades,
发展了许多，几十年，
but the breakthroughs
但突破
are often most recent years.
通常是最近几年。
More than self driven cars
不仅仅是自驾车
now we have proven others can
现在我们已经证明其他人可以
drive safer than humans can drive and
驾驶比人类驾驶更安全
automotive companies and
汽车公司和
tech companies are struggling to
科技公司正在努力
find great engineers to keep up.
找到优秀的工程师跟上。
This is the self driven program and
这是自我驱动的程序和
when you are finished,
当你完成后，
you will have the skills to drawing
你将有绘画技巧
this cutting edge industry.
这个前沿的行业。
We are super excited
我们非常兴奋
to have you with us.
和你在一起。